SAGAR BETKAR

Mumbai, India (+91) 9702396398 | <u>sagarbetkar1994@gmail.com</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>Github</u> | <u>Website</u>

PROFILE DESCRIPTION

Full-Stack Developer with more than four years of experience developing responsive web applications, micro frontends & various integrations. A Can-do attitude, perseverance, and being a team player, gaining a little knowledge each day, always looking for a chance of self-improvement, and keeping an eye on what's next. Good understanding & Most of my work so far has been written with Javascript, React, Angular, Node.js, Express, MongoDB.

SKILLS

Languages HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Typescript, GraphQL, Sass, PHP.

Libraries and React, Redux, Mobx, Socket.io, Node.js, Ant design, MongoDB,

Databases MySQL.

Frameworks Angular, Next.js, Nest.js, Express, React-Bootstrap, Bootstrap,

AngularJS, Slim.

Project Skills Agile Methodology, Mentoring, Communication, Pair Programming,

Time Management, Team player.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Knoxpo, Mumbai, India

March 2019 – Present

Full Stack Developer

- Developed various responsive web applications, micro frontends, REST & GraphQL APIs & Integrated various apis. Eg:- Twilio, Stripe, Redis, RabbitMQ etc.
- Experience in an agile environment (Scrum, Kanban). Close Collaboration with designers, product managers, VPs & clients for better understanding.
- Experience in PRs reviews, pair programming, working under pressure & tight timelines.
- Technologies used so far:- React, Typescript, GraphQL, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Socket.io, Ant design, Angular, Next.js etc.
- Deployed web application using Docker on Google Cloud Platform.

Freelancer, Mumbai, India

August 2018 – February 2019

Full Stack Developer

- Developed Web Applications & APIs using technologies such as HTML5, SCSS, Angular, Typescript, Node.js, MongoDB, Express (MEAN Stack), Github & deployed on AWS.
- Close collaboration with clients for a better workflow.

3Y Ventures LLP (tag8), Mumbai, India

January 2018 – August 2018

Software Developer

- Developed an in-house B2B web application for placing an order of companies products & generating invoices.
- Used technologies such as AngularJs, PHP (Slim framework), SQL, Github & deployed on AWS.
- Worked on restructuring the official website and other in-house projects.

Stalkerscode Private Limited, Mumbai, India

August 2017 - December 2017

Web Developer

- Developed responsive websites using the latest technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap & PHP.
- Interacting with clients and designers to deliver the best web experiences.

INTERNSHIPS

Software Developer internship at 3Y Ventures LLP (tag8) through Internshala Developed an in-house B2B web application for placing an order of companies products.
[January 2018 – March 2018]

EDUCATION

University of Mumbai, India

July 2012 – June 2017

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science.

LANGUAGES

- **English** (Professional Fluency)
- Marathi (native speaker)
- **Hindi** (native speaker)